micrositemasters.com 2018-10-20

# Microsite Masters Rank Tracker - Accurate SEO Keyword Tracking

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Microsite Masters collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.micrositemasters.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Microsite Masters, LLC. 

**Personal Information**

We may collect personal information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources that we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, their name, email address, phone number, address, payment information, and other information that we may deem desirable to collect for the purposes of delivering or enhancing our Site or services. Users may, however, visit our Site without providing this information. We will collect personal information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site-related activities, and they will be unable to enroll in the service that we provide. 

We may use the information we collect for internal reporting services, to create reports about rankings with all identifying information and keywords removed, and to help us help you. Namely, our service is designed to help you understand where you stand with your marketing efforts and to help us know how we can better serve you. Thus, we aggregate certain personal and non personally identifiable information, in an anonymized form, to help us develop new products, services, enhance existing ones, and create reports. 

**Non-personal information**

We may collect non-personal information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal information may include the browser name, the type of computer, IP address, operating system, Internet Service Provider, and other technical information about Users' means of visiting our Site. 

**Web Browser Cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance Users' experiences. Users' web browsers place cookies on their hard drives in order to allow us to distinguish user accounts for security and privacy reasons, and to conduct marketing campaigns that we think may interest certain Users. For these reasons, enabling cookies is mandatory for full functionality of our Site and service. 

**How We Use Collected Information**

Microsite Masters collects and uses Users' personal information for the following purposes: 

-To personalize user experience   
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 

\- To improve our Site   
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 

\- To send periodic emails   
The email addresses Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

**How We Protect Your Information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

Our Site is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users. 

**Sharing Your Personal Information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users' personal information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above and for any other purpose we deem desirable for our business operations or our Users. 

**Third Party Websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. We recommend that you review those websites' Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, or analogous documents, so that you understand your rights in relation to your use of those websites. 

**Compliance With Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, we never attempt to collect or maintain information at our Site from those who are under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. If you become aware of a user who is under the age of 13 years of age, please contact us with full details. If you have been reported as being under 13, and we determine that the report has merit, we will request that you provide proof of age with a copy of government identification, and will discontinue providing our service if you do not comply. 

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

Microsite Masters has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy each time that you visit our website or use our service, and remain aware of any amendments. 

**Your Acceptance Of These Terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy means that you accept those changes. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your   
dealings with this site, please contact us at:   
Microsite Masters, LLC   
http://www.micrositemasters.com   
621 East Pratt Street Suite 605, Baltimore, MD, 21202   
staff@micrositemasters.com 

**This document was last updated on August 12th, 2012**
